<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ModMetaData>
  <name>RimArchive-In Progress</name>
  <author>Auxia</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>Auxia.Weaponpack.BlueArchive</packageId>
  <description>
    Before All:This mod is now still in progress.Some contents are not actually installed in this mod.Current status does not represent the final quality.
	须知:本模组仍在制作当中，部分内容暂未实装进模组中，目前状态不代表最终品质。
	
	Waring:Data unblanced(yet).
	警告：模组大量元素仍未做平衡处理。
	This mod includes serveral weapons from Blue Archive.
	All the game textures are hand-painted.In the future,I will introduce more Blue Archive weapons and more interesting element into the games.Have fun.;)
	
	本模组包含了许多来自碧蓝档案的武器
	模组中的所有贴图均是手绘，在未来，我会制作更多的碧蓝档案武器与有趣的元素;)
	Till 2023/1/17 Mod published
	We got these students weapon:
	目前已实装的学生武器：
	Abydos:
	Hoshino 星野
	Serika 芹香
	Shiroko 白子
	
    Gehenna:
	Hina 日奈
	
	Hyakkiyako:
	Izuna 泉奈
	
	Millennium:
	Aris 爱丽丝
	Hibiki 响
	Karin 花凛
	Midori 小绿
	Momoi 桃井
	Neru 尼禄
	Yuzu 柚子
	
	Trinity:
	Hifumi 日富美
	Koharu 小春
	Tsurugi 鹤城
	（only weapon contained）
	（以上学生仅包含武器）
	QnA:
	Q:Will there be more students weapons appear in this mod?
	A:Sure.Most weapons will appear in the game,and the priority of pistols is low.
	Q:未来会有更多学生的武器出现在模组中吗？
	A：是的，大多数学生的武器都会陆陆续续地加入到模组中，并且手枪的优先度要低于其他武器。
	
	Q：CE？
	A:Not yet.I'm not a CE player and i have no assistant（Im a new one）.I have to focus on weapons but I'm sure it will be soon.
	Q：CE?
	A：暂不支持，原因是我很少玩CE而且所有工作全由我一个人完成（我是新手）.我得将大多精力集中在制作有趣的武器上，但我相信很快它就会支持了！
	
	Q:Will we got students apparel for our pawns?
	A:Yes,But it takes a lot of time to paint beautiful textures.
	Q：以后会有学生服饰加入当中吗？
	A：是的，但是绘制且保证贴图质量需要大量时间。
	
	Q:Many weapons data is imbalanced.Will this change?
	A:Unfortunately,i am not a RimworldPro.Most data changes could depend on players feedback.Post ur advise in comment area,i will fix the unreasonable place and thx.:D
	Q：很多武器的武器不是太强就是太弱，未来会改吗？
	A：糟糕的是我玩Rimworld玩的比较懒，对数值这方面拿捏的不是很好，所以许多数值需要依赖玩家的反馈，把改动建议发在讨论区，感谢所有提供建议的好兄弟！
	
	Q:Any place required attention?
	A:This mod support Chinese language only(so far).The English support should be coming soon.
	Q：还有什么其它需要注意的吗？
	A：玩的开心;)
	
	写在最后：本模组未来可能会发展为综合性拓展包，这个模组是娱乐向的，所以有些武器可能会不适合某些游戏环境。
	我会尽可能地将这个模组完善并做好。国内的碧蓝档案爱好者想要提建议的话可以百度贴吧：@普通的机车族战士。
	
	干杯！
	Cheers！
  </description>
  <modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>erdelf.humanoidalienraces</packageId>
			<displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>erdelf.humanoidalienraces</li>
		<li>ceteam.combatextended</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>